王柏元 BEN WANG

Engineer

0966527002



Xindian



I am always passionate about self-development. In the past three years in HTC, I have continued to study the knowledge of network management and various technologies. Also work with our team and became familiar with the process of website setup, development and deployment, and have the opportunity to mantain and develop multiple projects. It was a great experience for me to learn so much and work with so many excellent people. I believe that I can use my experience and the knowledges to help the team grow. Also, I look forward to the new values and growth we can bring together.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Engineer HTC | 2019

Maintaining EC projects.

- VIVE shopping site, VIVELAND webpos system, VR developer hub etc.
- Develop new features based on internal requests.
- Communicate with PM, DevOps and QA to ensure the update fulfill the request.

Data Transfer

- Obtain data from multiple databases and generate digital reports.
- · Data transfer with other dept using API

Self Study

- Study the most efficient development techniques and share with my team.
- · Data transfer with other dept using API

Specialist HTC | 2017 - 2019

After graduation, I was transferred to full-time job. In addition to the original work, I also started to assist in the development. Participated in many projects.

Contractor HTC | 2017 - 2017

I was hired as a contractor while studying. In charge of maintaining the official website using front-end languages.

Database Operator

Mandarin Library & Information Service Co., Ltd. | 2015 - 2016

I work here as a part time job when I was a student. Mainly responsible for creating and maintaining the citation data for TCI-HSS (Taiwan Citation index - Human and Social Sciences). The citation is the reference material of various academic papers like journal articles, doctoral thesis. Used as one of a standard to calculate the value of academic papers.

PROJECTS

Django Content manager

We implement Django as content management system for HTC official website. I test and maintain the system as a content manager. Responsible for the product information setting and translation of the global official website, and also to adjust the website content according to the activity time between regions.

Developer Hub Developer

This website is for developers, and the information inside includes various VR-related SDKs and development document. While the developer browses the website, we expect to contact with the developer and collect their information. For example, if the developer wants to cooperate with HTC. They can apply for a cooperation form and ask for various kind of help.

At the time we implement Salesforce for our CRM. I was there to help transfer the old developer data to Salesforce, and established a form builder system associated with Salesforce in the background. All fields correspond to the Salesforce API and can be directly store into the platform after submit.

VIVE eCommerce Developer

HTC has used magento 1 as its online trading platform for a long time, but until 2019 it was decided to upgrade to mangento 2, which is a big project. In addition to M1 and M2 is fundamentally disign in different way, the system configuration for different regions is also different. There is no way to upgrade all of the countries at once. And I was lucky to have the chance to participate in the upgration of TW and EU.

VIVELAND Webpos Developer

This system is an online cash register. It help Syntrend VIVELAND to record their daily revenue. I was in charge to maintain the system and create various report for sales team to reference. Worth memthion is that webpos only had the ability to record revenue. So we let it integrate with VIVELAND's member system to achieve cumulative

EDUCATION

HTC | 2019 - 2020 Information and Communication

Shih Hsin University 2013 - 2017

SKILLS

Technical

Python/PHP

JavaScript/Vue/Knockout

CSS/Bootstrap/Sass

MySQL/MariaDB/PosgreSQL/MongoDB

Laravel/Magento

Django/Flask

linux/ubuntu/nginx/docker

Object-oriented design

Design and implement database structures

Soft Skills

Strong problem solver

Continuous improvement

Focus on teamwork

Effective communication

Strong sense responsibility

LANGUAGES

Chinese (Native)

English (Fluent)

INTERESTS

Learning

Badmintion

Travelling

member spending. Hope that in the future, specific discounts can be made for specific members according to the amount of consumption.



